<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<office:document-content xmlns:officeooo="http://openoffice.org/2009/office" xmlns:css3t="http://www.w3.org/TR/css3-text/" xmlns:grddl="http://www.w3.org/2003/g/data-view#" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:formx="urn:openoffice:names:experimental:ooxml-odf-interop:xmlns:form:1.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:rpt="http://openoffice.org/2005/report" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:chart="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:chart:1.0" xmlns:svg="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:svg-compatible:1.0" xmlns:draw="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:drawing:1.0" xmlns:text="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:text:1.0" xmlns:oooc="http://openoffice.org/2004/calc" xmlns:style="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:style:1.0" xmlns:ooow="http://openoffice.org/2004/writer" xmlns:meta="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:meta:1.0" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:fo="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:xsl-fo-compatible:1.0" xmlns:ooo="http://openoffice.org/2004/office" xmlns:office="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:office:1.0" xmlns:dr3d="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:dr3d:1.0" xmlns:table="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:table:1.0" xmlns:number="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:datastyle:1.0" xmlns:of="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:of:1.2" xmlns:calcext="urn:org:documentfoundation:names:experimental:calc:xmlns:calcext:1.0" xmlns:tableooo="http://openoffice.org/2009/table" xmlns:drawooo="http://openoffice.org/2010/draw" xmlns:loext="urn:org:documentfoundation:names:experimental:office:xmlns:loext:1.0" xmlns:dom="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:field="urn:openoffice:names:experimental:ooo-ms-interop:xmlns:field:1.0" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:math="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:form="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:form:1.0" xmlns:script="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:script:1.0" xmlns:xforms="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" office:version="1.3"><office:scripts/><office:font-face-decls><style:font-face style:name="Liberation Sans" svg:font-family="&apos;Liberation Sans&apos;" style:font-family-generic="swiss" style:font-pitch="variable"/><style:font-face style:name="Liberation Serif" svg:font-family="&apos;Liberation Serif&apos;" style:font-family-generic="roman" style:font-pitch="variable"/><style:font-face style:name="Lohit Devanagari" svg:font-family="&apos;Lohit Devanagari&apos;"/><style:font-face style:name="Lohit Devanagari1" svg:font-family="&apos;Lohit Devanagari&apos;" style:font-family-generic="system" style:font-pitch="variable"/><style:font-face style:name="Noto Sans CJK SC" svg:font-family="&apos;Noto Sans CJK SC&apos;" style:font-family-generic="system" style:font-pitch="variable"/><style:font-face style:name="Noto Serif CJK SC" svg:font-family="&apos;Noto Serif CJK SC&apos;" style:font-family-generic="system" style:font-pitch="variable"/></office:font-face-decls><office:automatic-styles><style:style style:name="P1" style:family="paragraph" style:parent-style-name="Heading_20_3"><style:text-properties officeooo:paragraph-rsid="000bcb78"/></style:style><style:style style:name="T1" style:family="text"><style:text-properties fo:color="#800000" loext:opacity="100%"/></style:style><style:style style:name="T2" style:family="text"><style:text-properties fo:font-weight="bold"/></style:style><style:style style:name="Sect1" style:family="section"><style:section-properties fo:margin-left="0cm" fo:margin-right="0cm" style:editable="false"><style:columns fo:column-count="1" fo:column-gap="0cm"/></style:section-properties></style:style></office:automatic-styles><office:body><office:text text:use-soft-page-breaks="true"><text:sequence-decls><text:sequence-decl text:display-outline-level="0" text:name="Illustration"/><text:sequence-decl text:display-outline-level="0" text:name="Table"/><text:sequence-decl text:display-outline-level="0" text:name="Text"/><text:sequence-decl text:display-outline-level="0" text:name="Drawing"/><text:sequence-decl text:display-outline-level="0" text:name="Figure"/></text:sequence-decls><text:h text:style-name="Heading_20_3" text:outline-level="3">Profile</text:h><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">Separate hostels are provided for boys and girls situated within walking distance from the college for convenience. The hostels are prepared to be an extended home. the hostel facilitates completely support students to carry out serious study and to grow physically, intellectually and psychology. The college tradition and discipline is also extended to the hostels. </text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">Students can enjoy the homely atmosphere along with hygienically maintained top class facilities.Round the clock security ensures that our students are safe at KSSEM and the hostels are absolutely free from ragging and the boarders are guaranteed with comfortable &amp; peaceful stay. </text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">For boys from KSSEM there is college bus facility to reach the boys hostel in KSSEM campus</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">As the girls Hostel is right opposite to KSSEM, there will be college bus facility for the girls from KSSEM as well</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">Our hostel are more than home away from homes which provides the feeling of one&apos;s family.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">Along with huge walk around campus, monitored by securities, CCTV camera for internal monitoring , well furnished spacious &amp; clean rooms, hygienic kitchen &amp; dining area, proactive indoor GameSpot, elevators, well equipped gym, interactive TV room, all of which with all time power and power generator for backup power and water facility with solar water heater pumps, RO treated water from the top tasks for all buildings , double RO treated drinking water, friendly visitors lobby, playground, most time available housekeeping support staff and special separate visitors room for the parents or guardians who visit the students.</text:p><text:h text:style-name="P1" text:outline-level="3">L. Krishna A. <text:s text:c="3"/></text:h><text:h text:style-name="P1" text:outline-level="3">Girls Hostel Supervisor <text:s text:c="28"/></text:h><text:h text:style-name="P1" text:outline-level="3"><text:s/>Balakrishna Naidu </text:h><text:h text:style-name="P1" text:outline-level="3"><text:s text:c="2"/>Boys Hostel Supervisor</text:h><text:h text:style-name="Heading_20_4" text:outline-level="4"/><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">Our warm greetings to all the KSSEM hostel students, their parents living in India, and other parts of the world.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">It feels delighted to welcome you all to be a part of KSSEM family that strives to provide students a homely and healthy atmosphere with complete Safety and security in the hostel. </text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">At the hostels of KSSEM, we not only take efforts to provide its students a neat and clean environment and a comfortable place to live in, but encourage them to live in discipline. We understand discipline is the key to success and career building, hence we promote self-discipline among students.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">We know hostel life is a union of diverse cultures and different upbringings, which blends into a harmony for a rich and memorable experience. We provide atmosphere where they can learn, laugh and live to the fullest. The caretakers ensure that the students get a clean, green and relaxed atmosphere. We promote green sustainability inside the hostel premises.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body"><text:soft-page-break/>Hostels are Designed in a student friendly manner, not only with comfortable spacious rooms, clean and hygiene modern attached bathroom. The rooms are also well furnished with wardrobe and study table, to meet the need of students. </text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">The hostels are literally homes for those who want to share, care and prosper. </text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">The six story building of boys hostel is built with 200 rooms of 2 sharing each with 400 students capacity. The five story building of girls hostel consists of 54 rooms of three sharing each 162 students capacity.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">Students from various ethnic roots &amp; languages can stay together and learn a lot to get quite an exposure to diversity.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">A common study area for academic discussions for innovative thinking with 400 square meters of space in boys hostel and 100 square meters space in girls hostel </text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">The reading rooms has a provision of daily news papers and magazines.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">The diversity intend to promote the interactions and collaboration with an unlike communion of ideas, life style and better student celebrating differences and exposure.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">The common area of over 1000sq. meters in boys hostel is been provided for indoor games consisting of table-tennis, carrom boards, chess and other indoor games for the recreation of the students. The girls staying in hostel can access the indoor games center inside the KSSEM campus. </text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">We have well equipped gym in the boys hostel for students which signifies not only studies but also physical fitness too is important to keep the mind balanced and happy. To enhance the social and recreational facilities there is various clamps and fitness activities.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">The gym has latest machines and equipments for the students including treadmills, stationary bikes, elliptical machines, rowing machines and a wide range of weights and plates.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">We have a common TV room where the students can get together to get a part of entertainment like movies and sports matches, in the leasure time and holidays.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">The boys hostel Tv room has a seating capacity of 150 students, whereas the girls hostel has the Tv mounted in the mess area itself.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">The food bringing people together, the hostel&apos;s food/dining area brings nutritisious and healthy cusine with North Indian, South Indian, pure vegetarian meals.The hostel premises comprises of a separate dining facility for hostel residents. The hostel mess has a separate dining hall and a well-equipped, Clean and hygienic kitchen. As healthy food is the key of healthy mind and when mind is healthy students can concentrate on their studies and other academic activities, this objective is being fulfilled by the Hostel Mess having 200 students at a time. </text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">The food served is fresh and of high quality which meets the nutritional quality standards.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">Breakfast, lunch and dinner included.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">Both boys and girls hostel has a spacious visitor&apos;s lobby where the Tv is mounted along with newspapers and magazines for the refreshment of visitors. </text:p><text:h text:style-name="Heading_20_3" text:outline-level="3">Hostel Fees</text:h><text:section text:style-name="Sect1" text:name="fees"><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body">For queries related to hostel admissions and fees , please contact KSSEM office.</text:p></text:section><text:p text:style-name="Text_20_body"><text:soft-page-break/></text:p></office:text></office:body></office:document-content>